キルアに会うまで！ それまでは絶対に帰らない！
That's him. How did you find him?
フフっ。 それでは　こちらへ　どうぞ。
Hell if I'll tell you, fool. You in the shadows, was it through your power?
キルアに会うために 越えなければならない障害を
Are you some kind of freak? I recently completed a very entertaining battle.
目の当たりにしたゴン達
I'm quite sensitive at the moment...
彼らが連れて行かれる先に 一体　何が？
To calm myself down, I rather feel like messing up
a complete stranger.
今夜は　もう遅い。
Come on out.
まぁ　泊まって行きなさい。
Was my Zetsu not good enough?
さぁ　どうぞ。
Here is Troupe member #4. In other words, your replacement.
おい　戻ったよ！ ほう　客人とは珍しいな。
My name is Kalluto. I cannot tell you how my power works,
but we found him by using it.
彼は　シークアント。
Ah...
私と一緒に ここで働いております。
You look very appetizing as well. Be careful.
こんばんは！
He certainly isn't picky.
フン。
Hisoka, you'd better succeed.
ゼブロに気に入られるとは 大した連中だ。
You people are so tedious.
まっ　ゆっくりして行きな。
I certainly shall, for my own benefit.
といっても　この家じゃ そうも　いかねえだろうがな。
Are you serious about fighting the boss? Of course I am.
ハハハ！　こいつは傑作だ。
Once you finish your job here,
you can die, for all I care.
あいにく　こちとら 大真面目でな！
And if I kill Chrollo, then what?
忠告しといてやるよ 諦めて　とっとと帰りな。
That would be impossible. But I'll answer your question.
何だと!? ゼブロから 「試しの門」のこと聞いてんだろ？
I would pursue you to the ends
of the Earth to kill you.
だったら　ここが　どういう所か 分かったはずだ。
I like the sound of that...
簡単に　たどり着けないことは 分かったよ。
Our objective is
でも　俺は帰らない キルアに会うまでは。
to obtain Breath of Archangel,
currently monopolized by Team Genthru.
俺…　キルアが辛い時に そばにいてあげられなかった。
We must force them to transform a card, or we won't have a chance to use our Voucher. And that's where Team Gon comes in.
あの時　俺が　そばにいたら
While they may not have the
strength to win outright, they are highly likely to deal serious
damage to a member of Team Genthru.
絶対に　キルアを止めたのに…。
If they're forced to use a Breath of Archangel, Voucher
A voucher that can be
exchanged for Breath
of Archangel. Can only
be obtained when
Breath of Archangel
has attained its card
transformation limit. our Voucher will become a Breath of Archangel.
キルアは　俺の大切な友達なんだ！
Breath of Archangel
An angel that cures any
mortal injury or terminal
illness with one breath.
But angel only appears once. After that... We only need Lucky Alexandrite!
フフ…　分かりました。
And if we can buy three weeks for those kids, they'll trade the card to us!
では　しばらく　ここで 特訓してみませんか？
Yes. Right, it's time. Let's get going.
あの門は　たとえ３人がかりでも 開けばＯＫなんです。
I believe I told you to come alone.
短期間でも 訓練次第では不可能ではない。
We weren't able to make a decision, so we kept discussing it on our way here.
どうです？
And we've finally reached a consensus.
試されるのは不本意だけど…。
We choose to fight!
他に方法がないのなら。
Levy on!
やるしかねえな！
Accompany on!
うん！
To Antokiba!
では　早速　皆さんに 着てもらうものがあります。
Book.
ん？
Check your cards. Book!
ぐふっ。 何だ？　この重さ…！
It's okay. They only stole some useless
cards from my free slots. Same here.
それで５０ｋｇあります。
I didn't lose anything important.
寝る時以外は　いつも
Guess that settles it. We take their cards and kill them.
着ていてください。 えっ!?
They'll put up a fight.
慣れたら徐々に重くします。 はぁ!?
Huh? I don't know what's happened to them...
さぁ　お茶をどうぞ。
But their resolve was written all over their faces.
ふん！　あれ？ その湯飲みは２０ｋｇ このポットも４０ｋｇあります。
Six copies of Accompany, twenty-four of Return, nine copies of Castle Gate, and two of Magnetic Force.
この家の家具　食器 全て２０ｋｇ以上ありますよ。
I spent all our money on them. Okay, then we'll meet up in three days.
なるほど これが特訓ということか。
Use that time to earn money
and buy the cards we need.
無駄　無駄。
Got it.
どうせ　２３日で 音をあげるのが　オチだ。
Do you think they'll come after us?
んだと!?
Not immediately.
シークアント　交代の時間は とうに過ぎてるんだがな。
We now have nearly twice the number
of Accompany cards as Genthru.
おっと　そうだったな。
If they use Clairvoyant Serpent, they'll see that.
すみません 悪い奴じゃないんですが…。
Just you watch, Genthru...
ところで…　トイレって　どこ？ そこに見える扉です。
This is how a Single Star Hunter fights.
ええ！ もちろん５００ｋｇあります。
Gyo! Too slow!
５００…!?
Don't stop to think after I grab your arm.
え！　ウッソ！
Act the second you feel my touch! Osu!
漏れる！
Too slow. Osu!
ダメだよ　ママ。
If you can elevate around
at least that high, you pass.
こいつ ちっとも反省しちゃいない。
Okay!
さっさと帰ればいいのに 「試しの門」に挑戦するそうだぜ。
That training is a lot harder, given that it's only a level higher.
ゴンが来てる…？
Naturally... Because this is
really level-five training.
ミルキ！　また余計なことを！ あのね　キル…。
Five? Are you sure you should skip levels like that? Well, it's a gamble.
今まで黙っていたのか！
If it doesn't work, we'll have wasted
the three weeks we were given.
ママに向かって その言い草は　何だ!? お前は　お黙りと言うのに！
If we followed the proper sequence,
he could reach level three easily.
言う必要がないと思ったのよ キル。
But that wouldn't do him any
good in actual combat.
あの門を開くなんて 無理に決まってるわ。
He needs an Emitter attack that
can push an opponent back
開くさ。 えっ？
several meters with a direct hit.
ゴンなら　開くさ。
It must be that strong for
him to use it as a weapon.
まぁ　それは素晴らしいわ でもね　たとえ門が開いても ここに　たどり着くまで…。 ゴンは
So you jumped to level five... But even if he clears the training, the ability to send enemies flying
isn't a desicively lethal weapon.
あいつは…　きっと来る。 必ず　ここまで　たどり着く。
Exactly right. It's only meant to give him more options. So have you made any progress on a plan?
待て　ゴン。
I'll introduce you to my power.
お前は見学だ。 えっ　何で？
Magical Esthetician Cookie-chan.
まずは　腕を治すことが先決だろ。
She specializes in providing
massages of pure pleasure.
俺とクラピカで 開くことができりゃ　問題なし！ 任せとけ！ うん。
She'll burn off excess fat and guide both
your body and your soul to paradise.
行くぜ　クラピカ！ ああ！ うぅ！ ふん…。
When her aura, transformed into
special lotion, is applied to the skin, it makes your skin look younger.
ぐぁ…。 ぐぅ…。
She can also use acupressure massage
to cleanse your body internally.
無理に決まってるだろ。 くぅ…。 うぅ…。
Constipation, stiff shoulders, chills...
any anomaly you have will vanish! That's it?
ダメだ　びくともしない。 クソ！ しかし　まぁ まだ　特訓は始まったばかりだ！
Of course not! She can also do chiropractic massages,
meditative massages, rolling massages... And there's still much more!
頑張れば　何とかなる！
Are you an idiot?!
いいなぁ　能天気な頭で…。
That's totally worthless! What are you talking about?!
ぬお！ ぐお…。
They're using hit and run tactics,
then making clean escapes.
ハァハァ…。 ハァハァ…。
We immediately move to a different location,
but before long, they find us. They're using Nen.
いくらやっても無駄だって いいかげん　気づいたらどうだ？ そう思うんだったら　見てねえで てめぇの仕事をしてたら どうなんだ！
If they aren't using a spell,
like homing or tracking, one of their members must have
a Nen power similar to radar.
チッ　はぁ…。
We can't defend against that!
ゴンは仲間だ。 あ？
What do we do?
ハァハァ…。 その仲間が 大切な友達に会いたがっている。
We'll just have to use some force.
最後まで 手を貸すのは当然だろう。
That's one copy of Accompany...
ああ！ ぬお！ おぉ！
Okay, we'll set Steal on his binder...
ぐぁ…。 くっ。 ったく！
He hasn't met them before. Then he's clean.
やみくもに押せば いいってもんじゃねえだろうが！ タイミングを合わせろ！
Hey, have you heard of the bombers?
最大限の力を 両方の扉　同時に与えないと
Yes, I've heard the rumors... We are the bombers.
扉は開かねえんだよ！ フフっ。
I just set a bomb on you.
タイミングを合わせて…。
I can kill you from anywhere, anytime I wish.
最大限の力を　両方の扉　同時に。 よし！ うん！
If you don't want to die,
bring me the cards I request.
サン！ サン！
Hey, here's another Accompany!
うぐっ。 ぐぅ！
I'll set Steal in here....
だぁ！ がはっ。
Kess
Tsezgerra
Rodriot
レオリオ！　クラピカ！
Uh-oh! Too bad!
ハァハァ…。 ハァ。
You're out!
何？　「試しの門」が…？
Contact
Communicate with one target
player (encountered within the
game) via your Book. (Connection
maintained for a maximum
of 3 minutes. May only be
broken by player who uses card.)
[LR][NORM] This is pure speculation. But they must be aware of me.
それで？ [TEL]　あっ　いや
They've realized that someone new is
providing cards to Team Tsezgerra.
ご報告をしたまでで　特には…。 分かった。 [TEL] 相変わらず無愛想な奴。
So to flush me out, they check the binders of
anyone who exits the store, disposing of everyone who's met one of you. They also steal their cards.
ふんっ　ふんっ　よっと。
And any players that they free
once cleared of suspicion are forced to collect cards for them.
ふんっ。 うん！
By eliminating suspects and taking their cards, they also cut off our supply.
２人とも。
They're killing three birds with one stone.
今日は　そのベストを脱いで 押してみなさい。
Got it. We'll try to track their movements.
おっ　ありがてぇ！
Get away from there and
wait for us to contact you.
イチ　ニの…。 サン！ サン！
They don't appear to be leaving Masadora.
ふん！ ふう！ ぬお！ ぐぁ！
Okay, next we check their cards.
ぬう！ くっ。
Together, those three have sixteen copies of Accompany
and two of Magnetic Force.
くっ　うあ！ ぬう！
That's a significant increase...
おっ。
At this pace, they'll catch up
to us in four to five days.
ぐあ！
But we expected that.
ハァ…　うっ　ふう！
They're saying they won't move
until they have enough cards.
チクショ ここから　びくともしねえ！
Everything is going well.
もうひと踏ん張りだ　レオリオ！ 分かってるよ！
Twelve days left.
ゴン！ 何やってんだ　お前！　その左腕…。 大丈夫！　もう　治ったから！
It's not working...
治ったって…。 ホントかよ　ゴン！
Listen to me.
うん！
While training, see yourself firing a water pistol.
それより 呼吸を合わせるんでしょ？
You build up aura within your body,
then shoot it from your palm!
ああ…。 よし！　押そう！ 行くぜ！ イチ。 ニの…。
The greater your power,
the stronger the aura you fire.
サン！
You want to release all the aura
you've kept closed up inside.
うお！
The total amount of refined
aura you apply to the attack, and the speed, power, and timing
you apply to the release...
開く。 フフっ。
You need all of those elements
to land the attack you'll require.
わっ　うわ！ 痛ってぇ。
It's too hard!
ハァハァ…。 ハァハァ…。
I just don't get how you push the aura
in your body out of your hand...
開いた。
He hasn't made any progress for ten days.
よっしゃ！
Maybe you should have let
him start from level two.
やったな　ゴン！ うん！
We still have ten more days...
屋敷は山のどこかに 立っているはずです。
If we give Team Tsezgerra Lucky Alexandrite, they'll only be missing two cards.
お恥ずかしい話 ２０年　勤めていて
We still need over thirty...
実は 山まで行ったことがないんだよ。 役に立たなくて　すまないね。
We can just take them from Genthru by force.
ううん　とんでもない。
Gon would never accept that...
ゼブロさん　シークアントさん お世話になりました。
And we still have to figure out
how to defeat Genthru first.
フフフ…。
That's true.
ホントに　ありがとう！ さようなら！
So is this big enough?
大した連中だ。
We now have forty-eight copies of Accompany.
彼らなら　屋敷まで たどり着けるんじゃないかな？ アッハッハ…！　無理だな 死にに行くようなもんだ。
If you total their Accompany, Return, and Magnetic Force cards,
they only have forty-five cards.
それは　３年前の経験からかい？
Now they can't evade us. Let us start a game of tag we cannot lose.
全滅させられたんだぜ。
They're coming our way at an incredible speed!
嫌ってほど 思い知らされたからなぁ…。
We move according to the plan!
悪かったな…。
Accompany on!
ふぅ。
To Masadora!
化け物ばっかりさ 雇い主も　使用人も。
Accompany on! Tsezgerra!
「試しの門」が開いたと。 はい。
Accompany on! To Soufrabi!
キルは　今が一番大事な時。
Accompany on! Tsezgerra!
他の者を近づけてはなりません！ ましてや
Accompany on!
友達など無用のもの！ 分かってるわね。
To Masadora! Accompany on! Tsezgerra!
出て行きなさい。
To Soufrabi!
あなた達がいる場所は　私有地よ。 断りなく立ち入ることは まかり通らないの。
Damn, we only have five days left...
ちゃんと電話したよ 「試しの門」から通って来たし。
Don't you have any advice that
could help him break through?
執事室が　入ることを 許したわけではないでしょ？
The sensation of aura flowing through the body
じゃ　どうしたら許可が貰えるの？
is different for everyone.
友達だって言っても つないでくれないのにさ！ さぁ？　許可した前例がないから。
If I give him advice from my own perception
and he makes incorrect assumptions, it could end up hurting more than helping.
大目に見るのは　そこまでよ。
How many do we have left? Seven copies of Accompany.
この線を　一歩でも越えたら 実力で排除します。
They aren't coming... Did they give up? No way. They're taking their time to throw us off.
ゴン！　クッソ！
How's it going there? You were right.
レオリオ！　クラピカ！
Sub and Bara have appeared. Most likely the real ones.
手を出しちゃダメだよ 俺に任せて。 痛った。
They're speculating that I'll try to buy
cards while they're playing tag.
俺達　君と争う気は全然ないんだ。
Which means it's Genthru and a couple
of fakes that are chasing you.
キルアに会いたいだけだから。
Then Tsezgerra's predictions were accurate!
私は　雇い主の命令に従うだけよ。
Right now, Genthru is alone,
while there are four of us.
何度　来ても無駄よ。
Time's up.
絶対に　ここは通さない。
I came up with a plan for defeating them.
うぅ…。
But... But...
絶対に通る…。
Uh, well...
キルアに会うんだ！
I think I've almost got it. Maybe... No, it isn't happening.
((おかえりなさいませ キルア様))
So the plan is... To use this. Huh?
)
You'll have to learn this the hard way. Until you get it down to perfection.
We're out of Accompany cards...
)
Use Return!
うっ　うぅ…。
Perhaps... Okay, come back.
やめてよ…。
If they follow us outside the game,
we can fend them off at the mansion.
もう来ないで！
If they don't follow us, we just have
to wait until the time limit is up.
いいかげんにしてよ！ 無駄なのは分かるでしょ！
We just have to ask Mr. Battera what he wants.
あんた達も止めてよ！ 仲間なん…。
Okay, let's go!
何で　こんなことを しなきゃならないんだ！
No one's here.
ねぇ。 えっ？
Sabazushi! Keep it down...
もう　足　入ってるよ 殴らなくていいの？
I was taking a nap. A nap?
君は　ミケとは違う。
What happened to everyone else?
どんなに感情を隠そうとしたって ちゃんと心がある。
They left. Mr. Battera canceled the whole thing.
キルアの名前を出した時 一瞬だけど　目が優しくなった。
We received an intermediary fee
and a cancellation fee. But I stayed behind because I
thought I should inform you.
お願い…。
We're so close!
キルア様を…
We're close to beating the game! It doesn't matter...
助けてあげ…。
Doesn't matter anymore.
まったく…　使用人が 何を言ってるのかしら。
My lawyers have been instructed to pay you.
まるで私達が キルをいじめてたみたいに…。
You can do whatever you want with the cards.
ただの クソ見習のくせして失礼な…。
So now, just leave me alone...
あなたがゴンね イルミから話は聞いてます。
Damn!
あなた方が邸内に来ていることも キルは知ってますよ。
What's going on? I don't know. Why did this happen?
でも　今は会えない。
Since their ring data won't disappear.
ようやく　邸内に入ったゴン達
Team Tsezgerra has given Gon and his
friends the time that they promised.
だが　その前に立ちふさがった 最大の壁は…
But awaiting them was a
situation they didn't expect.